let FruitTeaQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "Which fruit teas have the same recipe?",
        "option1": "Mango Green Tea, Lychee Black Tea, Kiwi Green Tea.",
        "option2": "Mango Green Tea, Guava Black Tea, Hawaiian Fruit Tea.",
        "option3": "Mango Green Tea, Grapefruit Green Tea, White Peach Green Tea.",
        "option4": "Mango Green Tea, Passion Fruit Green Tea, Peach Black Tea.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which option is correct?",
        "option1": "You use 50% ice to make ALL fruit teas.",
        "option2": "You use 80% ice to make ALL fruit teas.",
        "option3": "You use 60% ice to make ALL fruit teas.",
        "option4": "Not all the above.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How much sugar and fruit puree goes into a regular size Grapefruit Green Tea?",
        "option1": "0.6 sugar and 1.5 grapefruit puree.",
        "option2": "0.5 sugar and 1.2 grapefruit puree.",
        "option3": "no sugar and 1.5 grapefruit puree.",
        "option4": "1.0 sugar and 1.2 grapefruit puree.",
        "answer": 1
    },
      
    {
        "question": "How much sugar and fruit puree goes into a regular size Mango Green Tea?",
        "option1": "1.0 sugar and 0.8 mango puree.",
        "option2": "1.2 sugar and 1.2 mango puree.",
        "option3": "1.2 sugar and 1.5 mango puree.",
        "option4": "0.8 sugar and 1.2 mango puree.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How much sugar and fruit puree goes into a large size Mango Green Tea?",
        "option1": "1.2 sugar and 1.5 mango puree.",
        "option2": "1.2 sugar and 1.8 mango puree.",
        "option3": "1.2 sugar and 2.5 mango puree.",
        "option4": "1.2 sugar and 1.2 mango puree.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Besides ice and sugar, what are the other 4 ingredients in the Hawaiian Fruit Tea?",
        "option1": "White Peach, Fruit Tea, Black Tea, and ice water.",
        "option2": "Peach, Fruit Tea, Oolong Tea, and ice water.",
        "option3": "Peach, Fruit Tea, Black Tea, and ice water.",
        "option4": "White Peach, Fruit Tea, Oolong Tea, and ice water.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How would you describe the flavor of Lychee to a customer?",
        "option1": "Heavy, delicate, sour, and fragnant.",
        "option2": "Savory, delicate, sweet, and fragnant.",
        "option3": "Light, delicate, sweet, and fragnant.",
        "option4": "Light, delicate, bitter, and fragnant.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which option is best to describe the order of steps in making a fruit tea?",
        "option1": "Place ice in the serving cup, add sugar, add puree, add tea, shake, and seal.",
        "option2": "Place ice in the shaker, add sugar, add tea, shake, and pour into cup.",
        "option3": "Place ice in the shaker, add sugar, add puree, add tea, shake, and pour into cup.",
        "option4": "Place ice in the serving cup, add puree, add tea, shake, and seal.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which option is correct?",
        "option1": "Fruit Teas cannot be made Hot.",
        "option2": "Fruit Teas can be made Hot or Cold.",
        "option3": "Fruit Teas can only be made Hot.",
        "option4": "Fruit Teas cannot be made Hot or Cold.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between White Peach and Peach?",
        "option1": "White Peach is more sour in flavor.",
        "option2": "White Peach is more light and delicate in flavor. Peach is more sweet and taste like southern peach.",
        "option3": "White Peach is more sweet and taste like southern peach. Peach is more light and delicate in flavor.",
        "option4": "White Peach is more sweet and fragnant. Peach is more light and fragnant.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Are we able to change the fruit tea base from green to black/water or black to green/water?",
        "option1": "No. We can only use a certain tea base in our Fruit Teas.",
        "option2": "No, because it will ruin the original flavor of the Fruit Teas.",
        "option3": "Yes. We can change the fruit tea base with any tea base that we have in store.",
        "option4": "Yes. However, do not offer it up as an option to the customer unless they asked.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How would you describe Hawaiian Fruit Tea to the customer?",
        "option1": "It contains half green tea and water and tastes sour.",
        "option2": "It made with green tea and tastes citrusy.",
        "option3": "It contains half black tea and water and tastes like fruit punch.",
        "option4": "It made with black tea and make it tastes bitter. ",
        "answer": 3
    }
];